<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.alivegr" name="AliveGR" version="3.0.0~alpha9" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" version="3.0.6"/>
<!--        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.logos" version="1.0.2"/>-->
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.192"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl.pluginsgr" version="0.1.11"/>
<!--        <import addon="script.module.urldispatcher" version="1.0.0"/>-->
        <import addon="script.module.scrapetube" version="2.6.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.netclient" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.unicache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.parsers" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="4.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.fuzzywuzzy" version="0.0.17"/>
        <import addon="script.module.websocket" version="1.6.4"/>
<!--        <import addon="script.module.json_repair" version="0.52.5"/>-->
<!--        <import addon="script.module.m3u8" version="6.0.0"/>-->
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="7.4.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="router.py">
        <provides>video audio executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/modules/service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR addon</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon allowing streaming content available mostly in Greek language.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
On demand content is scraped from various websites and is freely available on the internet on public domains. This software acts only as a search engine.
Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is" with no warranty.</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο AliveGR</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR επιτρέπει τη θέαση ροών με περιεχόμενο κυρίως εις την Ελληνική γλώσσα.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δε φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο σε δημόσιους ιστότοπους. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί μόνο ως μηχανή αναζήτησης.
Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων Kodi ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι" χωρίς καμία εγγύηση καλής λειτουργίας.</disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://github.com/Twilight0/plugin.video.alivegr/discussions</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/Twilight0/plugin.video.alivegr</source>
        <website>https://alivegr.net/</website>
        <news>+ [COLOR green]3.0.X series[/COLOR] [I]10-03-2026 - 11-05-2026[/I]
- Update live TV section with new channels, fewer groups, and new remote source
- Removed dependency for logos resource addon, logos are now pulled from a network source and cached locally
- Major refactoring, removed legacy and compatibility code
- Removed a lot of old and unused code and features, and simplified the overall structure of the addon
- New artwork and icon theme (gemini)
- M3U8 module dependency removed and stream choice is now either adaptive or best
- Groups and indexing methods can now be changes from either a context menu or from a dedicated button on top
- Added the option to autostart the addon on Kodi launch (defaults to off)
- Added additional source for movies (greekfun)
- Updated Privacy Policy, DMCA texts
- Genres are now translated
- Add localhost proxy for tricky url requests and resolving of streams (initially designed to handle websocket streams)</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/main_menu.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/live_streams.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/networks.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/movies.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/tv_series.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/kids_movies.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/search.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/newspapers_frontpages.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/music.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
